Let us analyze the latest numbers of ICICI LBR General Insurance Company.
So before that let me
tell you one thing, quickly subscribe to the channel.  It may take
1 minute or 10 seconds
and then you will not miss any
results because results are very
important.  Mainly the losses that occur are
because you do
not analyze the financials.  It's
not your fault.  You don't understand and no
one explains it in a way that should be understandable.
But from now on I will
tell you all these things.  So subscribe to the channel.
Ok?  So we
look at the numbers.  We see the numbers in all the charts.
So let us
look at the numbers quarterly.  So here
we look at sales and expenses.  So here the
sales have increased compared to the previous quarter.  It's all right.
Yes, if I
tell you quickly according to my own opinion, the sales are
quite good.  This means that the company's sales are continuously
growing slowly.  And if we
look at the expenses here, the expenses are also
fine.  There have been fewer expenses compared to the previous quarter.
And if we
look at it quarterly, the number is Rs 651 crore.
Sales in the last quarter were Rs 6396 crore and
in this quarter it was Rs 6396 crore.  So the sales have
increased compared to the previous quarter and yes there
is a good growth, there is no problem in sales
and the company is also increasing the operating profit quite well.   There
is no loss.  The company's operating
profit has increased.  And if
seen quarterly, the company's net profit has increased from Rs 69 crore to Rs 981 crore.
Instead of saying main operating
net profit, I mistakenly
said net profit,
operating profit which comes from the main business.  Ok
?  And if we look at the other income of the company, it is Rs
13 crore.  There is no significant other income
coming in.  The company's interest is negligible.
And if we look at the net
profit of the company here, then the
net profit of the company is continuously increasing.  Ok?
So, the net profit is not fluctuating much but
yes, there is growth within the company
and the numbers are correct.  If we
look at it quarterly, the net profit in the last quarter
was Rs 510 crore and in this quarter it is Rs
747 crore.  And we should compare this with last
year's quarter.  This is how much has happened
here in this June quarter,
747 and that is worth 580 crores.
And if we look at last March and this March, the
last quarter was weak but
in this quarter the company has posted good numbers.
If we look at the yearly data, then the
sales
of the company are continuously increasing here.  It's a
good thing.  The business
growth in the company is quite good.  And
you can see our numbers if you want to.  But
yes, we should see whether the company is growing
or not.  The big players
see growth.  The operating profit
of the company is also continuously increasing.  And if we
look at other income, it is negligible here.   If you get
good other income then it is a good thing, but if you don't get it then it is not a
bad thing.  Ok?   If
we look at the interest, there is no equal interest on the company
because ICICI Lar means it is in the insurance business,
so there is no such interest.  The company has such a net
profit, see it is continuously increasing.  It is the
best company.  It is a good company.  So that's why
net profit increases.  Otherwise, bad
companies never increase their net profit.
Ok?  So the net profit
is increasing.  You can see the numbers are
year on year compared to the previous quarter.
So you should look at these numbers.  But yes
we should see main growth.  After that we should
go to the technical side.  And look at the reserves the
company has taken from where to where.  Meaning that the
company started its business from here
and took its money here while growing it
and here the name of borrowings
is equal and the fixed assets of the company have
reduced here as compared to last year
but yes they have to open offices here
and CWI is also running here worth Rs 74 crores
that when it gets completed it will
come here and this number will
grow a little, the investment of the company is
continuously increasing because
here only investment happens
because here the company invests the
money and with that it
grows the insurance business.  Here also, the
investment should mainly
increase continuously, if I tell you straight away.  So that's a good thing.  Is
continuously increasing.  There is growth in the company.  If we
look at the share holding, then all these
strong players have share holding.
All holdings Mainly.  Now
why am I saying strong player weak player
brother?  You must have heard about
strong players for the first time. Mainly, the big players
see
how many strong players and weak
players are there in the company?  So if we look at the strong players,
we have FIIs, DIs,
promoters and those who have more than 1% holding in the public, all of them
come under strong players.  So
look, all the strong players are holding this company.
So they will let this company go
down a bit.  The
company will take you up the charts.  Whenever it comes down, we will
pick it up.  Ok?  And the Player of the Week is
always constantly falling down.  So that's a
good thing.  Stock players are
well-positioned in this company.  So the numbers are
quite good according to me.  We should see growth.
We should focus on the numbers.
But not only this, charts tell us
everything.  Ok?  So the numbers
are good and do subscribe to the channel and
do tell us your view in the comments.
Ok?  So see you
in the next video.  Till then take care of yourself.